question_data = [
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
 "question": "\'The Division Bell\' is the final album of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "In \'League of Legends\', there exists four different types of Dragon.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
 "question": "In \'Star Trek\', Klaang is a typical Klingon male.", "correct_answer": "True",
 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
 "question": "In \'Avatar: The Last Airbender\' and \'The Legend of Korra\', Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "SCP-173 was the first SCP article written for the web-based collaborative fiction project known as the \'SCP Foundation\'",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "In \'Super Mario Bros.\', the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False",
 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                  "question": "In the \'S.T.A.L.K.E.R.\' series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  \'the Zone\'.",
                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
 "question": "The Ceratosaurus, a dinosaur known for having a horn on the top of its nose, is also known to be a decendent of the Tyrannosaurus Rex.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
 "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
 "question": "\'Mongolia\' was a part of the now non-existent U.S.S.R.", "correct_answer": "False",
 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                  "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
 "question": "Early RAM was directly seated onto the motherboard and could not be easily removed.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
 "question": "Ottoman Empire was created in 1299.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
 "question": "The card game \'Munchkin\' won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
 "question": "The Roman god \'Jupiter\' was first known as \'Zeus\' to the Greeks.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.", "correct_answer": "False",
 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "\'Return to Castle Wolfenstein\' was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William \'B.J.\' Blazkowicz.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
 "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Art",
                                   "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.",
                                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "In the game \'Subnautica\', a \'Spadefish\' will attack you.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
 "question": "In 2019, Minecraft outsold Tetris to become the world&#039;s best-selling video game.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]